innpoints.com 2010-02-20

# InnPoints Worldwide [Privacy Policy]

**Effective as of June 1, 2009 **

This Privacy Policy applies to the following business: Electronic distribution, located on the World Wide Web at http:// www.innpoints.com (the "Website," "we," "our," or "us""). The Website is a unit of and operates as a separate line of business within, ABQ Direct, Inc. dba ("InnPoints Worldwide"). We respect the privacy of the personally identifiable information of the users of this Website (hereafter, â€œyouâ€ or â€œyourâ€). This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices available to you concerning the way that we use the information collected online at the Website. 

Type of Information Collected  
Any information you provide to the Website is completely voluntary; you are not required to provide any of the information requested at the Website. If you should to provide information, please take the time to read and understand this Privacy Policy. Please direct any questions you have after your review to the contact information provided below. You should not provide any information to the Website until you are satisfied that you understand this Privacy Policy and any questions you have about it have been answered. Even after you provide information to the Website and agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, be aware that you may revoke your affirmative consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time, simply by following the instructions in the â€œYour Choicesâ€ section below. 

Personally Identifiable Information  
During registration, the Website may request the following personally identifiable information from you: your name, street address, e-mail address, telephone number, date of birth, social security number and credit reference information. We may also request information about your use of, or interest in, the types of products and services offered by the third-party advertisers with whom we have partnered to offer you the products and services available at this Website and at other websites. We collect the personally identifiable information which you submit to the Website. 

How We Use Your Information  
WE MAY USE THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECTED AT THE WEBSITE FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE, INCLUDING SELLING OR TRANSFERRING SUCH INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES, SUCH AS INTERNET MARKETING COMPANIES. By submitting information to the Website, you expressly authorize and consent to and grant to us, our affiliates and partners the right to use your personal information for any legal purpose including, without limitation: (a) transferring your personal information to a third party advertiser (such as retailers or direct marketers); (b) marketing purposes such as sharing your information with financial service providers (such as mortgage lenders or brokers, insurance companies or title companies); (c) providing promotional offers to you by means of e-mail advertising, telemarketing, direct mail marketing, pop-ups, pop-unders, SMS cell phone text messaging, instant messaging and/or online banner advertising; (d) tracking compliance with both InnPointsâ€™ affiliate marketing terms and conditions and with the Website's terms and conditions, if any are so provided; and (f) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. 

To the extent Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, 15 U.S.C. 6802 (the "GLB Act") may apply to our services, this Privacy Policy is your initial "Privacy Notice" as defined under the GLB Act. By submitting personally identifiable information to us, you acknowledge receipt of this Privacy Notice and also consent to receive your annual Privacy Notice of the Privacy Policy, where required by federal law, via this Website, and/or via email (where you provided us with your email address), and/or via first class mail (if you provided your mailing address to the Website).

By submitting information to the Website, you agree to let us contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Website. You affirmatively consent and expressly authorize us and/or our affiliates or other third parties to transmit to you commercial messages via electronic mail, text messaging, instant messaging, or other electronic means, including to your mobile device, at the email address or other contact information you submit to the Website. Note that you may be charged by your mobile service provider for such messages, and will be obligated to pay any transmission costs, directly to your wireless service provider. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO RECEIVE MESSAGES FROM US OR OUR PARTNERS ON YOUR MOBILE DEVICE, DO NOT SUBMIT CONTACT INFORMATION TO THE WEBSITE THAT WOULD RESULT IN THE TRANMISSION OF SUCH MESSAGES TO YOUR MOBILE DEVICE. You may revoke your affirmative consent and authorization to receive commercial messages via such means at any time using the procedures described in this Privacy Policy.

BY AGREEING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU CONSENT TO DISCLOSURE OF ANY RECORD OR COMMUNICATION YOU PROVIDED TO US, TO ANY THIRD PARTY WHEN WE, IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION, DETERMINE THE DISCLOSURE TO BE APPROPRIATE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, TO MARKET PRODUCTS AND SERVICES OFFERED BY US OR THIRD-PARTIES, OR TO AFFECT OR ADMINISTER A TRANSACTION YOU INITIATED. We also reserve the right to release current or past member information in the event that we believe that this Website is being or has been used to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, is required to be disclosed pursuant to other legal process, or if we are sold or acquired.

You agree that your submission of personal information at the Website constitutes a purchase, inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR Part 310 (the "ATSR"). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, we or our designee retain the right and you hereby expressly authorize us and/or our designee to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR. Moreover, by registering with, making a purchase from, or requesting information from, a third party advertiser at or through the Website, such action shall constitute a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application with the respective third party advertiser for purposes of the ATSR and you may be contacted via e-mail, instant messaging, text messaging, direct mail and/or telephone by such third party advertiser.

We may share with third party advertisers certain Website usage information of individuals that have received targeted promotional campaigns for the purpose of formatting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics. For this purpose, we may track some of the pages that you visit on our Website through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs). By submitting information at and/or registering at this Website, you agree to allow us to share such Website usage information with third parties. Furthermore, your submission of personally identifiable information by registering with this Website shall be considered as your providing affirmative consent to become a member of our list(s), an opt-in, and as such you expressly waive any privacy protection or other benefit(s) afforded by any national or state "Do Not Call" or other similar lists or registries. Such waiver is void in jurisdictions that expressly do not allow such waiver of rights, and you may at any time request to be unsubscribed from our lists (please note that if you also opted in separately with any third parties, you should contact them directly in order to opt out of their email communication, following the instructions provided on their emails or similar communication to you, describing how to properly opt-out).

We also may use "cookies" to enhance your experience in using our Website. Cookies are text files that we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. By submitting information at and/or registering at this Website, you agree to allow us to use cookies to understand Website usage, to personalize your experience, and to improve the content and offerings on our Website. To find out more about cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. Even in the case where a user rejects a cookie, he or she may still use the Website.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the pages of this Website. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer or Safari), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Website and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Website usage, as well as to offer you products and services. We reserve the right to use aggregate or group data about our visitors for any lawful purpose. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and/or characteristics of our visitors as a group. By visiting and/or supplying your personal information at this Website, you agree to allow us to provide such aggregate data to third parties.

Third Party Links  
We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of any third party advertiser that may advertise at this Website. The businesses that advertise and/or place banner ads at this Website including, but not limited to, these third party advertisers, are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of each website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Website.

Your Choices  
During registration and/or when you submit personally identifiable information to us at the Website, you are giving us your affirmative consent to use and disclose such information pursuant to this notice and terms of this Privacy Policy. However, we provide you with an opportunity to request that we not share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties. If, at any time in the future, you would like to request that we not share your information with third parties, you may opt-out from such sharing practices by sending an email to info@innpoints.com. Please note that changing your preferences regarding the receipt of marketing communications from us will not prevent other companies with which we already have shared your information, including third party advertisers, from continuing to provide you with offers. When contacted by these companies, you should notify them directly of your choices regarding their use and sharing of your information. To opt-out from receiving any additional email communications regarding this Website, click here **enable click-through to opt-out page**. To opt-out from receiving any additional SMS text messages simply reply to any text message you receive from us with "STOP", "QUIT" or "END". To opt-out from receiving any additional instant messages simply click on the opt-out link appearing at the end of any instant message you receive from us and follow the basic prompts. In addition, please note that if you subsequently sign up on one of Hotel Smart Suite's websites for another product or service offerings, you may need to reconfirm any information sharing preferences that you have previously changed.

Your California Privacy Rights  
If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes, please click here **enable click-through to opt-out page** or email us at customerservice@innpointsworldwide.com. However, where California residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared with third party marketing partners, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with the law. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we agree not to share the social security number of California State residents with third-parties, if you have provided us with such information and identified yourself as a California resident, without first obtaining their consent to do so pursuant to the terms and conditions set forth in the California Financial Information Privacy Act ("CFIPA"). For purposes of compliance with the CFIPA, we will not share "nonpublic personal information" (as defined in the CFIPA) with our affiliates without providing California State residents with an annual notice explaining that we will be sharing this nonpublic personal information with our affiliates. To fully execute a CFIPA consent acknowledgement, click here **connect them to RIDER 1, below**.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits visitors to this Web Site, who are California residents, to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to HYPERLINK "mailto:info@innpoints.com" info@innpoints.com or write us at: ABQ Direct Inc. dba InnPoints Worldwide, 800 20th Street N.W., Suite B, Albuquerque, New Mexico 87104.

Important Information for Vermont Customers  
In accordance with Vermont law, we will not share information we collect about Vermont residents to nonaffiliated third-party companies except with the authorization or consent of the Vermont resident. By submitting personal information to us, you are providing your affirmative consent for us to sell, transfer, or otherwise disclose information we collect about you to affiliates and non-affiliated third-parties for the purposes identified in this policy. You may revoke your opt-in choice at any time by contacting us at HYPERLINK "mailto:info@innpoints.com" info@innpoints.com 

Minors  
This Website is not directed at individuals under the age of 18, nor do we knowingly collect information from individuals under the age of 18. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, this Website by individuals under 18 years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

Security  
We employ industry standard security measures to safeguard against unauthorized access to information that we collect online. When users submit sensitive information via the Website, we endeavor to keep this information protected both online and off-line. Online, we utilize SSL encryption software in connection with sensitive information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example a billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Access is not granted to employees who do not have a â€œneed to knowâ€ the information. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that there has been an information security breach. By submitting personally identifiable information to us, you are providing your affirmative consent to receive such notifications via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of breach and/or network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

Acceptance  
By using the Website and/or agreeing to receive information via e-mail from us, you agree to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will prominently post notice that the Privacy Policy has changed and provide a link to those changes on our Website so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Website and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

Electronic Signatures and Electronic Records  
By submitting your information and agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you understand and agree that you are agreeing to be bound by the Privacy Policy and all other agreements and terms and conditions found on the Website by using your electronic signature and that your electronic signature is as legally binding as a physical signature on paper. Furthermore, you are agreeing that you will use an electronic signature to accept electronic records regarding the services offered by this Website, including, but not limited to, this Privacy Policy.

You further agree and consent:  
1\. To receive agreements, applications, and other information that may be provided or otherwise available to you electronically. Included in those agreements, applications, and other information may be disclosures required by federal, state, and local laws and regulations, where allowed by such laws.  
2\. To be bound by the terms and conditions of the agreements, applications, and other information electronically provided to you by this Website.  
3\. To use and receive electronic records and electronic signatures in conducting business with the Website, including agreeing to the terms of the Privacy Policy.  
4\. That to electronically receive agreements, applications, and other information, you will need a compatible operating system, web browser, and email application, and you will need access to a printer or the ability to download information to keep copies of such documents for your records. By completing an application for a credit card, you represent and warrant that the operating systems, web browsers, and email applications you use are substantially compatible with the Website. You furthermore understand that you are indicating that you have the capability to access the agreements, applications, and other information and download or prints copies for your records.  
5\. For customer service or technical assistance regarding electronic records or electronic signatures, you may contact the Website by email at Info@innpoints.com.  
6\. You may request a paper copy of the agreements, applications, and other information by contacting the Website by email at info@innpoints.com. The Website will accommodate reasonable requests for paper copies without charging a fee for the paper copies.

Contact Us  
If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at [info@innpoints.com](mailto:info@innpoints.com)

****
